Congratulations once again.
>> Thank you so much.
>> No problem. And we're going to kick
things off with Cass followed by Alex
Zitlo.
>> Hey Zeith, congratulations.
>> Hey, how's it going?
>> Good. How about yourself?
>> Amazing. Couldn't be happier right now.
>> Um, I know that it's probably a lot to
take in right now, but wondering if
you've thought or let me go back. How
much you know about Nick Scott, just
another Penn State safety that's here.
And I know he might have been a little
before your time, but what will it be
like to kind of get in the backfield
with another Nitney Lion?
>> Uh, I mean, family is everything at Penn
State. So, uh, whether he was there when
I was there or not, that's just [snorts]
someone I've heard a lot about. Uh, and
Coach Franklin and the Penn State staff
has done nothing but, you know,
what's the word? Uh, recognize our
former players. So, Nick Scott is
someone who I've heard a ton of, very
familiar with his game, and I can't wait
to get in run with a, you know, older
vet and someone who went to the same
college as me.
And then was curious how much you had
talked to the Panthers throughout this
process and where you kind of see
yourself best fitting in
>> uh throughout this process. Uh it was
crazy because I did talk to the
Panthers, you know, uh during the
combine and throughout this process. But
at the end of the day, by the time it
came draft weekend, I didn't really
know, you know, where things were
heading. So, I couldn't be happier to,
you know, be in Carolina and represent
this blue right here.
>> And actually, I did have one more. I
just thought of it. Tell me about your
necklace.
>> Okay, Zigg, that's my nickname. Uh, got
it from my father. Uh, so his nickname
is Zigga. And then as I was growing up,
all my uncles used to call me Lil Zig,
uh, for short. So, it's kind of stuck
with me, uh, through high school and
Penn State and growing up. And that's
what a lot of my friends call me.
>> Awesome. Thank you. Congratulations.
>> Of course. Thank you.
>> What's up, man? Thanks for taking the
time.
>> Yep. Of course. How you doing?
>> I'm doing great. Um, uh, just curious,
how would you, in your own words,
describe your game?
>> I would describe my game as versatile,
fluent. Uh, I like going sideline to
sideline, making plays. I'm someone
that's going to be aggressive, be super
tough, and give him my all every single
time. You know, I strap my helmet up.
>> Absolutely. Is there um is there like
maybe a misconception about your game
that you're looking forward to
clarifying at the at the NFL level?
I mean, at the end of the day, you know,
football is a very, like I said,
versatile sport. So, there's things and
parts of my game that I definitely want
to improve on. And to me, I just feel
like that's that's every part of my
game, you know, being around
uh a well-rounded individual, whether
that's tackling, whether that's block
destruction, whether that's uh reading
the quarterback, uh just doing
everything I can in my power to be the
best version of myself in every single
category of this game to be uh the best
player on Sundays to help my team. So,
uh, any way I can grow and, you know,
become a better player and learn and,
you know, soak up everything that the
organ organization has for me, you know,
I can't wait. I'm willing to do it.
>> And then finally, last one for me, uh,
the Panthers obviously made the playoffs
last year for the first time. They
hosted a playoff game for the first time
in 10 years. Um, what do you think it'll
be like to join a an ascending team like
the Panthers?
>> I think it's amazing. I think everything
about it is a blessing. Uh, I just think
being able to grow up and, you know,
fight for this and, you know, go through
this my whole life to be able to get my
name called and to have be in this
moment, you know, and represent the
National Football League, uh, I think is
amazing. So, especially it being from,
you know, I'm from the East Coast. I'm
from Maryland, you know, so going not
too far, a little bit down south, uh, is
is amazing and I can't wait to, you
know, be a contender and and run it back
next year.
>> Awesome, man. Thanks. Yep. Hey, Joe
Person.
>> Hey, Zaki. Congrats, man.
>> Appreciate it. Thank you.
>> Hey, how difficult was it last season
going through Coach Franklin's firing? I
I know that's a guy, I'm sure, who
recruited you and take us through that
process.
>> Uh yes, sir. So, uh that's definitely
that's nothing I ever, you know,
experienced through my lifestyle as a
you know, player. I've been playing
football since I was 5 years old and I
never had a coach get fired uh in the
middle of the season. But I can say that
although it was un unfortunate um you
know it allowed me to become a leader uh
I was already a leader but it allowed me
to really step into that role you know
and you know all the leaders came
together just to fill that void um and I
think it made me tougher you know it was
up and down that I didn't know I had to
go through and there's a valley so get
being able to go through that and um
just prepare myself for the for the
league.
>> Cool. Yeah. Um, I I also want to ask you
too, like um I've seen a lot of the
analysts say that you have you have
solid speed but not top end speed. What
what would you say to that?
>> Uh what I'll say that is I'm I'm a
football player. Uh it's not something
that's I've dealt with just this year.
I've been deal my whole life. uh my
whole life as I've been someone who's
you know might have been doubted just
based on circumstance circumstances and
then I was someone that you know I'm
known as you know step foot in our
organization and give it everything I
have you know and be the best version of
myself and improve and
uh what I would say about the speed is
that you can make up with it with you
know football IQ and intelligence so you
know I've been around the game for a
long time uh constantly getting stronger
and faster and I can't wait to show my
speed in Carolina.
>> Appreciate it, man. Good luck,
>> sir. Thank you.
>> Mike Kane.
>> Hey, Zaki. Congratulations. Nice to meet
you.
>> Nice to meet you.
>> Um, have being 63 and having the length
that you do and having had to earn your
starting role at Penn State, you know,
those first three years being a cog on
on multiple different units. How much
did that how much does do your
intangibles and your experience and your
size help you on special teams
>> all around? I I went to uh you know Penn
State and that's something that coach
Franklin didn't take lightly. So uh I've
played Penn State uh pretty much
majority of the years at Penn State. Uh,
I have a ton of steps at um on special
teams and me personally, you know, with
my size and my intangibles, I feel like
I'm someone that can, you know, go on
special teams and um give it everything
I got and, you know, just impact the
team in in a positive way. Uh, and
really wherever I'm I'm needing,
wherever I'm needed, honestly. Uh, and
that can be anything. Coming in there,
uh, and doing everything I I can to be
the best version of myself and help this
team.
>> You're coming into a pretty versatile
position room. You obviously know that
they play a ton of zone coverage.
>> How comfortable would you feel playing
like dime linebacker or big nickel in in
in a specific package?
>> Uh yes, sir. So, um I'll be comfortable.
Like I said, I'm willing to do anything
uh anything I have to do to help this
organization and help this team and
whatever coach says he needs me to do to
learn and to, you know, to fit in, I'm
willing to do that. Uh full steam team
ahead and go from there.
Is there anybody during this process
that's in the pros that you've kind of
leaned on that you've kind of viewed as
like a mentor to kind of get you ready
for what you're about to accomplish?
>> Uh yes sir. So you know going to Penn
State I've been fortunate enough and
blessed to you know have a lot of
friends that's gone to the league the
last couple years. But someone some guys
who I talked to a lot is Joey Porter
Jier Brown and Jaylen Reed as well as
Kevin Winston Jr. You know all DBs all
players I've played with uh and learned
a lot from.
>> Awesome. Thank you.
>> Yep. Of course.
>> Any more questions for Zaki?
>> All right, Zaki, that seems to be the
question, all the questions that we have
for you today.
>> Thank you so much.
>> Thank you once again. Congratulations,
and we can't wait to have you here in
the Carolinas.
>> Thank you. I can't wait. Y'all have a
good one.
[music]